Today, we are going to learn how to make gourmet coffee in your home.
In this clip, I'm going to tell you a little bit about saving coffee and what's going to make your coffee taste best.
When you buy it, normally buy it whole bean.
Don't go for the already preground stuff.
You can get that at--like if you're going to a coffee shop or even if you buy a grinder, that's going to be your best bet like for that.
So then you can bring it home, grind it yourself so you're going to have that fresh-ground taste.
Also when you buy it, don't store it out in just anywhere, especially the freezer.
That's going to create moisture in the coffee bean and it's going to dry it out.
You don't want to leave that out though to open air.
You want to make sure that you're in a seal-tight container and then just put it in an area that is going to be roughly at household temperature around 72 degrees.
You can leave it there.
I would suggest having coffee for more than two weeks after it's opened.
If you buy these already sealed bags of the whole beans, you're going to be fine for keeping that for a while.
But once you opened it, that's when you need to be careful about how long you let it sit on your shelf.